Register of the Leopold Labedz papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Survey File, 1905-1987
  - Invoices, 1968 January 1-June 30 (Box-folder 70: 5-6)
  - Invoices for back issues, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 70: 7)
  - Konstantin Chernenko article, 1984 (Box-folder 70: 8)
  - Ledger with manuscripts received, 1967-1979 (Box-folder 71: 1)
  - Meetings, 1977 (Box-folder 71: 2)
  - Memoranda, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 71: 3)
  - Memorandum of agreement with publishers, 1986 (Box-folder 71: 4)
  - Memorandum and articles of association of Survey Magazine Limited, 1977 December 30 (Box-folder 71: 5)
  - Old information bulletin correspondence, 1961 (Box-folder 71: 6)
  - Order forms, undated (Box-folder 71: 7)
  - Orders for back issues, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 71: 8)
  - Oxford University Press, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 71: 9)
  - Oxford University Press, expenditure, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 71: 10)
  - Payments vouchers, 1969 April 1 - 1970 March 31 (Box-folder 71: 11)
  - Payments vouchers, 1969 April 1 - 1970 March 31 (Box-folder 72: 1-3)
  - Polish issues, reaction to Survey, 1980 (Box-folder 72: 4)
  - Previous issues list, undated (Box-folder 72: 5)
  - Production schedule, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 72: 6)
  - Proposed newsletter administrative records, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 72: 7)
  - Publication, 1978, undated (Box-folder 72: 8)
  - Reprint permissions, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 72: 9)
  - Reviews and comments, circa 1977 (Box-folder 72: 10)
  - Sub-letting of offices, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 72: 11)
  - Subscribers, 1959-1978 (Box-folder 72: 12)
  - Survey articles reproduced, 1961-1977 (Box-folder 72: 13)
  - Survey bulletin lists, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 72: 14)
  - Survey issues, 1971-1986
    Includes administrative documents and correspondence for various issues.
    - Issues 81-89, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 73: 1-9)
    - Issue 91/92, 1974 (Box-folder 73: 10)
    - Issues 93-97, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 74: 1-4)
    - Issues 107-108, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 74: 5-6)
    - Issues 111-114, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 74: 7-9)
    - Issues 116-125, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 75: 1-8)
  - Survey Magazine charitable trust, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 75: 9)
  - Survey negotiations, 1967 (Box-folder 75: 10)
  - Survey presentation file, 1960-1972 (Box-folder 75: 11)
  - Survey reprints, undated (Box-folder 76: 1)
  - Volkswagen accounting problem, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 76: 2)
  - 100th issue correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 76: 3-4)
  - Index cards with names of prospective contributors, undated (Box-folder 76: 5)
- Writings by Others, 1921-1987
  Manuscripts which were submitted to Survey for publication. Some manuscripts include correspondence, as well as edits made by Labedz. When possible, Labedz's original order was maintained.
  - Adamiak, R., 1978 (Box-folder 76: 6)
  - Adelman, Kenneth Lee, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 76: 7)
  - Adolf, Jacek, 1977 (Box-folder 76: 8)
  - Aeschliman, Michael D., 1979-1985 (Box-folder 76: 9)
  - Agursky, Mikhail, 1953-1982 (Box-folder 77: 1-2)
  - Aksyonov, Vassily, 1983 (Box-folder 77: 3)
  - Alexander, Robert, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 77: 4)
  - Alexeyeva, Ludmila, 1979 (Box-folder 77: 5)
  - Allum, P., 1977 (Box-folder 77: 6)
  - Amalrik, undated (Box-folder 77: 7)
  - Aman, Thomas L., 1970 (Box-folder 77: 8)
  - Ameri, undated (Box-folder 77: 9)
  - Anastasia, Paul, undated (Box-folder 77: 10)
  - Anin, David S., undated (Box-folder 77: 11)
  - Aravantinou, Mando, 1971 (Box-folder 77: 12)
  - Arden, J. E. M., undated (Box-folder 77: 13)
  - Are, G., 1977 (Box-folder 77: 14)
  - Argov, Shlomo, 1981 (Box-folder 77: 15)
  - Armstrong, undated (Box-folder 78: 1)
  - "Army General's Article Banned in Yugoslavia, Censored Text Smuggled to West,", 1970 (Box-folder 78: 2)
  - Arnovitz, Benton, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 78: 3)
  - Aron, Raymond, 1981 (Box-folder 78: 4)
  - Aspaturian, Vernon V., 1976 (Box-folder 78: 5)
  - Atkin, Muriel, 1983 (Box-folder 78: 6)
  - Ashleigh, Benjamin L., 1985 (Box-folder 78: 7)
  - Azmon, Yael, 1971 (Box-folder 78: 8)
  - Azrael, Jeremy, 1977 (Box-folder 78: 9)
  - Backer, John H., 1973-1977 (Box-folder 78: 10)
  - Bailey, George, 1986 (Box-folder 78: 11)
  - Balinska, Maria L., undated (Box-folder 78: 12)
  - Ball, George, 1973 (Box-folder 78: 13)
  - Barnett, Michael, 1981 (Box-folder 78: 14)
  - Barrett, Jeffrey, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 78: 15)
  - Barry, Donald D., undated (Box-folder 78: 16)
  - Bauman, Zygmunt, undated (Box-folder 78: 17)
  - Baumer, Max, 1976 (Box-folder 78: 18)
  - Beer, Fritz, 1968 (Box-folder 78: 19)
  - Bej, Emil, 1981 (Box-folder 78: 20)
  - Belinkov, Arkady, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 78: 21)
  - Bell, Daniel, 1970 (Box-folder 79: 1)
  - Belotserkovksy, Vadim, 1975 (Box-folder 79: 2)
  - Belskaya, A., 1973 (Box-folder 79: 3)
  - Bender, Peter, 1967 (Box-folder 79: 4)
  - Beneton, Philippe, undated (Box-folder 79: 5)
  - Ben-Shlomo, Ze'ev, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 79: 6)
  - Berg, Raissa L., 1981 (Box-folder 79: 7)
  - Berliner, Joseph S., 1978 (Box-folder 79: 8)
  - Berman, Jakub, undated (Box-folder 79: 9)
  - Besemeres, John, 1973 (Box-folder 79: 10)
  - Bethell, Nicholas, 1970 (Box-folder 79: 11)
  - Bettiza, E., undated (Box-folder 79: 12)
  - Bianco, Gino, undated (Box-folder 79: 13)
  - Bilinsky, Yaroslav, circa 1970 (Box-folder 80: 1)
  - Birman, Igor, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 80: 2-3)
  - Birnbaum, David, undated (Box-folder 80: 4)
  - Bitzer, Ronald, 1969 (Box-folder 80: 5)
  - Blackstock, Paul, undated (Box-folder 80: 6)
  - Blake, Patricia, undated (Box-folder 80: 7)
  - Bloch, Lionel, 1986 (Box-folder 80: 8)
  - Bobbio, Norberto, 1975 (Box-folder 80: 9)
  - Bociurkiw, Bohdan R., undated (Box-folder 80: 10)
  - Boesche, Roger, 1971 (Box-folder 80: 11)
  - Bogdanor, Vernon, undated (Box-folder 80: 12)
  - Boiter, Albert, 1975 (Box-folder 80: 13)
  - Bokov, Nikolai, 1977 (Box-folder 80: 14)
  - Bolloten, Burnett, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 80: 15)
  - Bondy, Francois, undated (Box-folder 81: 1)
  - Book on Africa by Brian Crozier, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 81: 2)
  - Book on Cuba by Theodore Draper, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 81: 3)
  - Book on the Cuban Revolution by Goldenberg, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 81: 4)
  - Bourdeaux, Michael, 1970 (Box-folder 81: 5)
  - Bowers, Stephen R., 1975-1977 (Box-folder 81: 6)
  - Bondys, 1981 (Box-folder 81: 7)
  - Braun, Aurel, 1977 (Box-folder 81: 8)
  - Breene, Robert G., 1986 (Box-folder 81: 9)
  - Broderson, Arvid, 1966 (Box-folder 82: 1)
  - Bromke, Adam, 1968 (Box-folder 82: 2)
  - Brown, Deming, undated (Box-folder 82: 3)
  - Bruegel, J. W., 1985 (Box-folder 82: 4)
  - Brumberg, Abraham, 1977 (Box-folder 82: 5)
  - Bryner, Cyril, 1968 (Box-folder 82: 6)
  - Bryson, Phillip J., 1974-1976 (Box-folder 82: 7)
  - Brzeziński, Zbigniew, circa 1985 (Box-folder 82: 8)
  - Buchanan, Paul G., 1984-1985 (Box-folder 82: 9)
  - Budiman, Arief, undated (Box-folder 82: 10)
  - Bukhanov, Victor, undated (Box-folder 82: 11)
  - Bukovsky, 1967 (Box-folder 82: 12)
  - Burke, S. M., 1971 (Box-folder 82: 13)
  - Burt, Richard, 1976 (Box-folder 82: 14)
  - Byrski, Zbigniew, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 82: 15)
  - Cafagna, Luciano, undated (Box-folder 83: 1)
  - Caroff, undated (Box-folder 83: 2-3)
  - Carter, F. W., 1967 (Box-folder 83: 4)
  - Carter, Stephen K., 1978 (Box-folder 83: 5)
  - Carynnyk, Marco, 1983 (Box-folder 83: 6)
  - Cate, Curtis, 1976 (Box-folder 83: 7)
  - Cazes, Bernard, undated (Box-folder 83: 8)
  - Chajn, Leon, 1985 (Box-folder 83: 9)
  - Chang, Pao-min, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 83: 10)
  - Chaplin, Arie, 1978 (Box-folder 83: 11)
  - Chazan, Naomi, 1971 (Box-folder 83: 12)
  - Checinski, Michael, 1975-1987 (Box-folder 83: 13)
  - Chenu, Roselyne, 1972 (Box-folder 83: 14)
  - Cherne, Leo, 1986 (Box-folder 83: 15)
  - Choi, Yearu H., undated (Box-folder 83: 16)
  - Chornovil, Vyacheslav, undated (Box-folder 83: 17)
  - Cienciala, Anna M., undated (Box-folder 84: 1)
  - Ciołkosz, Adam, 1966 (Box-folder 84: 2)
  - Ciuciura, Theodore B., 1923-1924 (Box-folder 84: 3)
  - Clark, Colin, 1969 (Box-folder 84: 4)
  - Clarke, Roger A., 1969 (Box-folder 84: 5)
  - Clemens, Walter, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 84: 6)
  - Cloud, Stanley, 1969 (Box-folder 84: 7)
  - Cock, Alan G., 1924-1975 (Box-folder 84: 8)
  - Cohen, Barry Mendel, 1980 (Box-folder 84: 9)
  - Coll, Alberto R., 1974 (Box-folder 84: 10)
  - Columbia University, undated (Box-folder 84: 11)
  - Connor, Walter D., 1970 (Box-folder 84: 12)
  - Conolly, Violet, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 84: 13)
  - Conquest, Robert, 1976 (Box-folder 84: 14)
  - Contemporary History in the Soviet Mirror, edited by Liliana Brisby, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 84: 15)
  - Copeland, Miles, 1985 (Box-folder 84: 16)
  - Costa, Nicholas J., 1986 (Box-folder 84: 17)
  - Courtney, Cathy, 1985 (Box-folder 84: 18)
  - Cotta, Sergio, 1975 (Box-folder 84: 19)
  - Craig, Richard, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 84: 20)
  - Crawley, Aiden and Virginia, 1962 (Box-folder 85: 1-2)
  - Crawshaw, Stephen, 1980 (Box-folder 85: 3)
  - Croan, Melvin, 1969, undated (Box-folder 85: 4)
  - Crowther, William, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 85: 5)
  - Cross, Sharyl, 1984, 1986 (Box-folder 85: 6)
  - Crozier, Brian, 1974 (Box-folder 85: 7)
  - Crumpacker, Amy, 1969 (Box-folder 85: 8)
  - The Cuban Revolution and Latin America by Goldenburg, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 85: 9)
  - Daalder, Hans, 1985 (Box-folder 85: 10)
  - Dadak, Kazimierz and Andrzej Bryk, 1984 (Box-folder 85: 11)
  - Dadrian, Vahakn N., 1967-1968 (Box-folder 85: 12)
  - Dagdzi-Suvarski, Dzengiz, 1970 (Box-folder 85: 13)
  - D'Agostino, Anthony, undated (Box-folder 86: 1)
  - Dahm, Helmut, 1967 (Box-folder 86: 2)
  - Dahrendorf, Ralf, 1986 (Box-folder 86: 3)
  - Dash, Samuel, 1972 (Box-folder 86: 4)
  - Davydov, Viktor, 1985 (Box-folder 86: 5)
  - Deane, Michael J., 1982 (Box-folder 86: 6)
  - Dejevsky, Mary, 1984 (Box-folder 86: 7)
  - Dima, Nicholas, 1986 (Box-folder 86: 8)
  - Dimant, Ilana, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 86: 9)
  - Dinerstein, Herbert S., 1972 (Box-folder 86: 10)
  - DIP report, undated (Box-folder 86: 11)
    Includes a report regarding the "Polish situation."
  - Djilas, Aleksa, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 86: 12)
  - Djilas, Milovan, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 86: 13)
  - Dobson, Richard B. and S. M. Lipset, 1972 (Box-folder 87: 1)
  - Dotsenko, Boris, 1970 (Box-folder 87: 2)
  - Drischler, William F., 1977-1979 (Box-folder 87: 3)
  - Duchêne, François and Leopold Labedz, undated (Box-folder 87: 4)
  - Dudintsev, Vladimir, 1971 (Box-folder 87: 5)
  - Dueval, Christian, 1954 (Box-folder 87: 6)
  - Dunham, Vera, undated (Box-folder 87: 7)
  - Dunlop, John B., 1977-1978 (Box-folder 87: 8)
  - Dunn, David, Dr., 1981-1987 (Box-folder 87: 9)
  - Dzhemilev, Mustafa, 1975 (Box-folder 87: 10)
  - Dzhirkvelov, Ilya, undated (Box-folder 87: 11)
  - Eckert, Robert E., 1968 (Box-folder 87: 12)
  - Eichler, Willi, undated (Box-folder 87: 13)
  - Eidelberg, Paul, circa 1980 (Box-folder 87: 14)
  - Eidlin, Fred, 1968-1978 (Box-folder 87: 15)
  - Ellman, M., 1977 (Box-folder 87: 16)
  - Engelstein, Laura, 1973 (Box-folder 87: 17)
  - Eran, Oded, 1971 (Box-folder 87: 18)
  - Ericson, Edward E., undated (Box-folder 87: 19)
  - Erickson, Karen, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 88: 1)
  - Erlich, Victor, 1967-1979 (Box-folder 88: 2)
  - Eto, Shinkichi, undated (Box-folder 88: 3)
  - Etuk, Jackson, 1973 (Box-folder 88: 4)
  - Evans, Alfred B., 1986 (Box-folder 88: 5)
  - Ezergailis, Andrew, 1968-1979 (Box-folder 88: 6)
  - Fainsod, Merle, undated (Box-folder 88: 7)
  - Falcoff, Mark, 1976 (Box-folder 88: 8)
  - Farrer, Grimes, 1974 (Box-folder 88: 9)
  - Fedoseyev, Victor and Rachel (Aleck), undated (Box-folder 88: 10)
  - Fejto, François, undated (Box-folder 88: 11)
  - Feldman, Paul, 1975 (Box-folder 88: 12)
  - Fetscher, Iring, undated (Box-folder 88: 13)
  - Feuer, Lewis S., 1967-1971 (Box-folder 88: 14)
  - Filipowicz, Halina, undated (Box-folder 88: 15)
  - Finkelshtein, E., undated (Box-folder 88: 16)
  - Fischer-Galati, Stephen, undated (Box-folder 88: 17)
  - Fisher, David James, 1974 (Box-folder 88: 18)
  - Fleron, Frederic J., 1976 (Box-folder 88: 19)
  - Floyd, David, 1977 (Box-folder 89: 1)
  - Flynn, Gregory A., 1975 (Box-folder 89: 2)
  - Fodor, Alexander, 1970 (Box-folder 89: 3)
  - Folts, David W., 1976 (Box-folder 89: 4)
  - Forgues, Pierre, undated (Box-folder 89: 5)
  - Forte, undated (Box-folder 89: 6)
  - Foster, Alan, undated (Box-folder 89: 7)
  - Fox, W. T. R., 1971 (Box-folder 89: 8)
  - Frankel, Edith Rogovin, 1981 (Box-folder 89: 9)
  - Friedgut, T. H., 1977 (Box-folder 89: 10)
  - Friedrich, Paul J., 1975 (Box-folder 89: 11)
  - Frolic, B. M., 1969 (Box-folder 89: 12)
  - Fryer, Eugene D., 1978 (Box-folder 89: 13)
  - Fukuyama, Francis, 1986 (Box-folder 89: 14)
  - Furlyska, Maria, 1983 (Box-folder 89: 15)
  - Fyvel, T. R., undated (Box-folder 89: 16)
  - Gaetan, Victor, 1980 (Box-folder 89: 17)
  - Galbraith, Kenneth, 1968 (Box-folder 89: 18)
  - Gall, Norman, undated (Box-folder 89: 19)
  - Gann, Lewis H., 1971 (Box-folder 89: 20)
  - Garrett, Stephan, undated (Box-folder 90: 1)
  - Garson, R. A., 1982 (Box-folder 90: 2)
  - Gay, James T., 1972 (Box-folder 90: 3)
  - Gazarian, Suren O., 1961 (Box-folder 90: 4-6)
  - Gelbert, Harry, 1986 (Box-folder 90: 7)
  - Gella, Aleksander, 1973 (Box-folder 90: 8)
  - Gellner, Ernest, undated (Box-folder 90: 9)
  - Gelman, Harry, 1986 (Box-folder 90: 10)
  - Gershman, Carl, 1980 (Box-folder 90: 11)
  - Gershon, David I., undated (Box-folder 90: 12)
  - Gerstenmaier, Cornelia, undated (Box-folder 90: 13)
  - Ghanayem, Ishaq I., 1975 (Box-folder 90: 14)
  - Gierow, Karl Ragnar, 1970 (Box-folder 90: 15)
  - Giller, Herbert, undated (Box-folder 91: 1)
  - Gillette, Philip, 1974 (Box-folder 91: 2)
  - Gitelman, Zvi Y., undated (Box-folder 91: 3)
  - Glad, John, undated (Box-folder 91: 4)
  - Glass, George A., 1979 (Box-folder 91: 5)
  - Gleberzon, William, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 91: 6)
  - Gleisner, Jeff, 1979 (Box-folder 91: 7)
  - Glenny, Michael, 1969 (Box-folder 91: 8)
  - Glogoczowski, Marek, undated (Box-folder 91: 9)
  - Glowacki, Janusz, 1983 (Box-folder 91: 10)
  - Gluzman, Semyon, undated (Box-folder 91: 11)
  - Godson, Joseph, undated (Box-folder 91: 12)
  - Godson, Roy, undated (Box-folder 91: 13)
  - Goetz-Stankiewicz, Marketa, 1977 (Box-folder 91: 14)
  - Golan, Galia, undated (Box-folder 91: 15)
  - Goldman, Marshall I., 1968 (Box-folder 92: 1)
  - Golomstock, I., 1986 (Box-folder 92: 2)
  - Gomulka, Stanislaw, 1983 (Box-folder 92: 3)
  - Gontarz, Ryszard, 1969 (Box-folder 92: 4)
  - Goodman, Elliot R., 1986 (Box-folder 92: 5)
  - Gowa, Joanne, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 92: 6)
  - Graham, Loren, 1971 (Box-folder 92: 7)
  - Greenfeld, Liah, 1986 (Box-folder 92: 8)
  - Gregory, Gene, 1967 (Box-folder 92: 9)
  - Gress, David, 1983 (Box-folder 92: 10)
  - Gribachev, N., 1970 (Box-folder 92: 11)
  - Griffith, William E., 1968-1975 (Box-folder 92: 12-13)
  - Grigorenko, A., 1975 (Box-folder 92: 14)
  - Gross, Jan T., 1978 (Box-folder 92: 15)
  - Gross, Natalie, 1987 (Box-folder 92: 16)
  - Grosser, Alfred, undated (Box-folder 92: 17)
  - Groth, Alexander J., 1978 (Box-folder 93: 1)
  - Gruenwald, Oskar, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 93: 2)
  - Guertner, Gary L., undated (Box-folder 93: 3)
  - Guha, Amalendu, 1975 (Box-folder 93: 4)
  - Guiducci, Roberto, undated (Box-folder 93: 5)
  - Gumpel, Liselotte, 1973 (Box-folder 93: 6)
  - Hadik, Laszlo, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 93: 7)
  - Hahn, Walter F., 1982 (Box-folder 93: 8)
  - Hahn, Werner F., 1971 (Box-folder 93: 9)
  - Haikio, Martti, undated (Box-folder 93: 10)
  - Hale, Julian, undated (Box-folder 93: 11)
  - Halle, Louis J., 1973 (Box-folder 93: 12)
  - Halperin, Charles J., 1981-1986 (Box-folder 93: 13)
  - Hamburg, Roger, undated (Box-folder 93: 14)
  - Hammett, Hugh B., undated (Box-folder 93: 15)
  - Hammond, Thomas T., undated (Box-folder 93: 16)
  - Hanson, P., 1977 (Box-folder 93: 17)
  - Harasymiw, Bohdan, 1975 (Box-folder 93: 18)
  - Hardt, John P., 1982 (Box-folder 93: 19)
  - Harris, Mary, 1963 (Box-folder 93: 20)
  - Hassner, Pierre, undated (Box-folder 94: 1)
  - Hattis-Rolef, Susan, 1974 (Box-folder 94: 2)
  - Haus, Leah, undated (Box-folder 94: 3)
  - Hayes, Nicholas, 1977 (Box-folder 94: 4)
  - Heald, David, undated (Box-folder 94: 5)
  - Heitmann, George, undated (Box-folder 94: 6)
  - Heller, Leonid, undated (Box-folder 94: 7)
  - Heller, Michael, 1921, 1984 (Box-folder 94: 8)
  - Henriksen, Thomas H., 1983 (Box-folder 94: 9)
  - Henze, Paul B., 1981-1982 (Box-folder 94: 10-11)
  - Henze, Paul B., The Ultimate Target: The Plot Against the Polish Pope, 1983 (Box-folder 95: 1-2)
  - Hines, John, undated (Box-folder 95: 3)
  - Hirszowicz, Maria, 1979 (Box-folder 95: 4)
  - Hochman, Jiri, 1985 (Box-folder 95: 5)
  - Hoffman, Erik P., 1969 (Box-folder 95: 6)
  - Hok, Mahbubul, 1976 (Box-folder 95: 7)
  - Hollander, Gayle Durham, 1974 (Box-folder 95: 8)
  - Hollinsworth, Barry, 1969 (Box-folder 95: 9)
  - Hook, Sidney, 1968 (Box-folder 95: 10)
  - Hooson, David J. M., undated (Box-folder 95: 11)
  - Horelick, Arnold L., 1974 (Box-folder 95: 12)
  - Horn, Robert C., 1975-1977 (Box-folder 95: 13)
  - Horowitz, Brook, 1986 (Box-folder 95: 14)
  - Hosking, Geoffrey, undated (Box-folder 95: 15)
  - Houghton, 1962 (Box-folder 95: 16)
  - Hovhannissian, E. H., undated (Box-folder 96: 1)
  - Hruby, Peter, circa 1960 (Box-folder 96: 2)
  - Hulsz, Edmund, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 96: 3)
  - Hunczak, Taras, undated (Box-folder 96: 4)
  - Hurwitz, Lee, 1985 (Box-folder 96: 5)
  - Husarska, Anna, undated (Box-folder 96: 6)
  - Hutchings, Raymond, 1969 (Box-folder 96: 7)
  - Hyde, Gordon, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 96: 8)
  - Ibarra, Armando Florez, undated (Box-folder 96: 9)
  - Igritsky, Yu. I., undated (Box-folder 96: 10)
  - Irvine, Reed, undated (Box-folder 96: 11)
  - Itzkov, Iosif, undated (Box-folder 96: 12)
  - Jackson, William M., 1968 (Box-folder 96: 13)
  - Jacobs, Dan N., 1975 (Box-folder 96: 14)
  - Jaffe, Phillip, 1971-1979 (Box-folder 96: 15)
  - Janos, Andrew C., 1977-1978 (Box-folder 96: 16)
  - Janowitz, Morris, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 96: 17)
  - Jelenski, K. A., 1961-1971 (Box-folder 96: 18)
  - Joffe, Josef, 1969 (Box-folder 97: 1)
  - Johns, Michael, 1987 (Box-folder 97: 2)
  - Johnson, Paul, 1986 (Box-folder 97: 3)
  - Jonas, A. David and Doris F., 1977 (Box-folder 97: 4)
  - Jonas, Gilbert, 1975 (Box-folder 97: 5)
  - Jones, Christopher D., 1974 (Box-folder 97: 6)
  - Jones, Jack, undated (Box-folder 97: 7)
  - Jones, Stephen, 1975-1987 (Box-folder 97: 8)
  - Jowitt, Kenneth T., 1982 (Box-folder 97: 9)
  - Kaczocha, Wlodzimierz, 1984 (Box-folder 97: 10)
  - Kalinovska, Milena, 1978 (Box-folder 97: 11)
  - Kamenka, Eugene, 1967 (Box-folder 97: 12)
  - Kaminska, Anna, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 97: 13-14)
  - Kaminski, Tadeusz, 1984 (Box-folder 98: 1)
  - Kanet, Roger E., 1969-1972 (Box-folder 98: 2)
  - Kankkonen, Peter, undated (Box-folder 98: 3)
  - Karklins, Rasma, 1980 (Box-folder 98: 4)
  - Karnow, Stanley, 1969 (Box-folder 98: 5)
  - Karpiński, Jakub, 1984 (Box-folder 98: 6)
  - Karpiński, Wojciech, 1985 (Box-folder 98: 7)
  - Karsow, Nina, 1982 (Box-folder 98: 8)
  - Kassalow, Everett M., undated (Box-folder 98: 9)
  - Kataoka, Tetsuya, 1969 (Box-folder 98: 10)
  - Katkov, Utechin, 1961 (Box-folder 98: 11)
  - Katus, J., undated (Box-folder 98: 12)
  - Katz, Mark N., 1970 (Box-folder 98: 13)
  - Katz, Zev, 1972 (Box-folder 98: 14)
  - Kaw, Marita, 1978 (Box-folder 98: 15)
  - Keep, John, 1969 (Box-folder 98: 16)
  - Kemp-Welch, A. (translator), 1981 (Box-folder 98: 17)
  - Kendall, Walter, undated (Box-folder 98: 18)
  - Kende, Peter, 1977 (Box-folder 98: 19)
  - Kent, Aileen, 1986 (Box-folder 98: 20)
  - Kernig, C. D., 1966 (Box-folder 99: 1)
  - Kindersley, Richard, undated (Box-folder 99: 2)
  - Kirby, E. Stuart, 1974 (Box-folder 99: 3)
  - Kisielewski, Stefan, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 99: 4)
  - Kissin, S. F., 1970 (Box-folder 99: 5)
  - Klehr, Harvey, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 99: 6)
  - Kleiner, I., undated (Box-folder 99: 7)
  - Klempski, Tymoteusz, undated (Box-folder 99: 8)
  - Kline, George, 1967 (Box-folder 99: 9)
  - Knight, Amy, 1985 (Box-folder 99: 10)
  - Knight, Robert, 1985 (Box-folder 99: 11)
  - Kober, Stanley, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 99: 12)
  - Koehler, Ludmila, 1975 (Box-folder 99: 13)
  - Kogan, E., 1984-1987 (Box-folder 99: 14)
  - Kolaja, Jiri, 1977 (Box-folder 99: 15)
  - Kolakowski, Leszek, 1957, 1985 (Box-folder 99: 16-17)
  - Kolkowicz, Roman, 1968 (Box-folder 99: 18)
  - Konieczynski, M., 1985 (Box-folder 99: 19)
  - Kontny, Pawel, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 99: 20)
  - Korakas, Mandis, undated (Box-folder 99: 21)
  - Korbonski, Andrzej, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 100: 1)
  - Korotich, Vitali, 1978 (Box-folder 100: 2)
  - Koryagin, Anatolii, undated (Box-folder 100: 3)
  - Kotkiewicz, Konstanty, undated (Box-folder 100: 4)
  - Kousoulas, D. George, undated (Box-folder 100: 5)
  - Kousseff, B. V., undated (Box-folder 100: 6)
  - Kovrig, undated (Box-folder 100: 7)
  - Kowalewski, David, 1976 (Box-folder 100: 8)
  - Kramer, John M., undated (Box-folder 100: 9)
  - Kramer, Kevin, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 100: 10)
  - Kramer, Mark N., undated (Box-folder 100: 11)
  - Krasnow, Wladyslaw, 1975 (Box-folder 100: 12)
  - Krejci, Jaroslav, 1974 (Box-folder 100: 13)
  - Krol, Marcin, 1978 (Box-folder 100: 14)
  - Krygier, Martin, 1985 (Box-folder 100: 15)
  - Kuczewski, Andre, 1984, undated (Box-folder 100: 16)
  - Kuron, Jacek, undated (Box-folder 100: 17)
  - Kushev, Evgeny, 1977 (Box-folder 100: 18)
  - Lafaurie, Serge, undated (Box-folder 100: 19)
  - Laird, Roy D., 1970 (Box-folder 100: 20)
  - Laloy, Jean, undated (Box-folder 100: 21)
  - Lambeth, Benjamin S., 1971 (Box-folder 100: 22)
  - Lammich, Siegfried, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 101: 1-2)
  - Laqueur, Walter, 1958-1973 (Box-folder 101: 3-4)
  - Larrabee, F. Stephen, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 101: 5)
  - Lasky, Melvin J., undated (Box-folder 101: 6)
  - Lathrop, Gregory L., 1982 (Box-folder 101: 7)
  - Lawrenson, Alec C., undated (Box-folder 101: 8)
  - Laychuk, J. L., 1973 (Box-folder 101: 9)
  - Layne, Christopher, undated (Box-folder 102: 1)
  - Layson, Walter W., 1972-1979 (Box-folder 102: 2)
  - Lazaris, Vladimir, 1978 (Box-folder 102: 3)
  - Lederer, Jiri, undated (Box-folder 102: 4)
  - Lee, Eric, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 102: 5)
  - Leggett, undated (Box-folder 102: 6)
  - Legvold, Robert, 1972 (Box-folder 102: 7)
  - Lehrman, Edgar H., 1969 (Box-folder 102: 8)
  - Leigh, John, 1968 (Box-folder 102: 9)
  - Leighton, Marian, 1986 (Box-folder 102: 10-11)
  - Lendvai, Paul, 1972 (Box-folder 102: 12)
  - Lester, Jeremy, 1985 (Box-folder 103: 1)
  - Lévesque, Jacques, 1972 (Box-folder 103: 2)
  - Lewis, W. Arthur, 1964 (Box-folder 103: 3)
  - Leys, Simon, 1979 (Box-folder 103: 4)
  - Lichtine, Saul, 1969 (Box-folder 103: 5)
  - Liehm, Antonin J., 1977 (Box-folder 103: 6)
  - Lincoln, W. Bruce, 1976 (Box-folder 103: 7)
  - Lindblad, J. Thomas, 1971 (Box-folder 103: 8)
  - Linton, Robert, 1971 (Box-folder 103: 9)
  - Linz, Juan J., circa 1970 (Box-folder 103: 10-12, 104: 1-2)
  - Lipinski, Edward, undated (Box-folder 104: 3)
  - Lipset, Seymour Martin, 1971 (Box-folder 104: 4)
  - Lisiecka, Alicja, 1974 (Box-folder 104: 5)
  - Litvinoff, Samuel, undated (Box-folder 104: 6)
  - Livingstone, A., undated (Box-folder 104: 7)
  - Loble, Eugene, 1970 (Box-folder 104: 8)
  - Loescher, undated (Box-folder 104: 9)
  - Lohr-Baily, Helga, 1969 (Box-folder 104: 10)
  - Lomax, Bill, 1984 (Box-folder 104: 11)
  - Long, James, 1981 (Box-folder 104: 12)
  - Lopez-Alves, Fernando, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 104: 13)
  - Loss, Richard, 1972 (Box-folder 104: 14)
  - Louis, Victor, 1969 (Box-folder 104: 15)
  - Loulis, John C., 1986 (Box-folder 105: 1)
  - Lowenthal, Richard, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 105: 2)
  - Lubis, Mochtar, 1961-1972 (Box-folder 105: 3)
  - Luck, David, 1968 (Box-folder 105: 4)
  - Ludanyi, Andrew, 1976 (Box-folder 105: 5)
  - Lukyanenko, 1978 (Box-folder 105: 6)
  - Lutz, James M., 1972 (Box-folder 105: 7)